Donald Hyde and Mary Hyde Eccles Autograph Collection (MS Hyde 10): Guide.
Donald Hyde and Mary Hyde Eccles Autograph Collection,
- Worsley, Richard, Sir, 1751-1805. Manuscript document, signed, Vencice (Italy), 1797 Jan. 26., (768a); 1s.
  Certificate concerning a Mr. and Mrs. Clarke.
- Wraxall, Nathaniel William, Sir, 1751-1831. Autograph letter, signed, Ramsgate (England), to James Lackington, 1810 Apr. 8., (769); 1s.
- Wraxall, Nathaniel William, Sir, 1751-1831. Autograph letter, signed, Frant, near Tunbridge Wells (England), to Edmond Malone, 1799 June 19., (770); 1s.
  Has seen only a few John Dryden letters in the collection owned by John Frederick Sackville, Duke of Dorset. Mounted with address panel.
- Young, Edward, 1683-1765. Certificate: document, signed, Welwyn (England), 1749 Jan. 11., (771); 1s.
  Certificate of residence for Mary Hallows.